{
	"category": "Music",
	"difficulty": "Senior",
	"subcategories": [
		{
			"subcategory": "Pop Music",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "Which Canadian pop star broke out with the 2012 hit single 'Call Me Maybe?'?",
					"answer": ["Carly Rae Jepsen", "Carly Jepsen", "Jepsen", "God"]
				},
				{
					"question": "As of July 2018, what Ed Sheeran song is the most streamed Spotify single of all time?",
					"answer": ["Shape of You"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What pop singer released the albums 'Artpop' and 'The Fame'?",
					"answer": ["Lady Gaga", "Gaga"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What New Zealand based singer's real name is Ella Marija Lani Yelich-O'Connor?",
					"answer": ["Lorde"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What country does pop singer Rihanna hail from?",
					"answer": ["Barbados"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"subcategory": "Classical Music",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "Which French impressionist composed 'Bolero'?",
					"answer": ["Maurice Ravel", "Ravel"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Who composed hthe music for the German National Anthem",
					"answer": ["Joseph Haydn", "Haydn"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What country does renowned composer Frederic Chopin hail from?",
					"answer": ["Poland"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"subcategory": "Musicals",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "Teyve is a character in what musical centered around a Jewish family?",
					"answer": ["Fiddler on the Roof"]
				},
				{
					"question": "What musical won the first Tony for Best Musical?",
					"answer": ["Kiss Me Kate"]
				},
				{
					"question": "West Side Story was directly based off of what Shakespeare play?",
					"answer": ["Romeo and Juliet"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"subcategory": "The Beatles",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "Which of the Beatles was the first to release a solo album?",
					"answer": ["George Harrison", "Harrison"]
				},
				{
					"question": "On February 9, 1964, what popular American television show did the Beatles perform on, kickstarting the British Invasion?",
					"answer": ["The Ed Sullivan Show", "Ed Sullivan Show", "Ed Sullivan"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which of the Beatles famously remarked that \"Ringo wasn't even the best drummer in The Beatles\"?",
					"answer": ["John Lennon", "Lennon"]
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"subcategory": "Hip-Hop",
			"questions": [
				{
					"question": "What Kendrick Lamar album lost out to Taylor Swift's 1989 for the 2016 Grammy Album of the Year?",
					"answer": ["To Pimp A Butterfly", "TPAB"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which famous rapper has the real name Curtis Jackson?",
					"answer": ["50 Cent"]
				},
				{
					"question": "Which influential hip hop group featured the members Chuck D and Flavor Flav?",
					"answer": ["Public Enemy"]
				}
			]
		}
	]
}